You, as you are now,
just keep supporting me.
What the hell, Rin?
After Isagi arrived,
his power has changed.
That shot just now was
a free attack I launched
to surpass Bachira's imagination
and became the key to the goal.
At that moment, I ran to the most extreme position,
and then was devoured by Rin.
Those three are amazing.
Facing world-class players,
they still managed to score immediately.
The collaboration that sparked a chemical reaction
between Isagi and Bachira,
and then Rin devoured both of their reactions.
Because of that match,
the three of them created this attacking formation.
Even against the world's top players,
they could still succeed.
Admirable, truly cool.
Yes. Such a noble triangle relationship.
A perfect style.
Let me join in
and make it a quadrilateral relationship.
No fair, it should be a pentagon relationship.
Join however you like.
Alright. How far can this go?
Until we win the match, of course.
Even though we scored,
it wasn't me who scored the goal.
Next, I will score the goal.
Bring it on, 17-year-old
representative of the France National Team!
Is he looking for a passing lane?
Is that okay?
(Julian Loki, France Representative)
There are clearly many openings around me.
Here it is! First step.
Super fast.
What kind of explosive initial speed is that?
Bachira!
At full throttle from the very start.
Without slowing down at all,
and dribbling with wide strides.
Crap, his strides are way too long!
Too late by the time I realized.
Your passing lanes are easily visible.
You may have figured it out,
but I'm faster.
Wha...
He accelerated again?
Is this the speed of Loki the Prodigy?
This is the level of the world's elite.
Loki, you're just playing alone. So unfair.
At least pass the ball to us.
Okay, but I'm already satisfied playing.
Finish it quickly and go take a shower.
Can we win?
He's just like a sprinter.
His speed is truly terrifying.
Don't talk pessimistically,
just pass the ball to me.
Are you scared of Loki's speed?
Lack of experience can
narrow your perspective.
I'll leave it to you, Brat.
Okay.
Bachira, stop him.
We'll attack together.
Okay.
(Pablo Cavasoz, Argentina Representative)
Flying out.
He's aiming for the gap between us.
A super-fast reverse spinning ball.
Aiming for this spot?
An aerial battle,
let me stop it.
(Dada Silva, Brazil Representative)
I'll crush you!
Even Aryu couldn't jump properly.
Crap, it fell right in front of the goal!
But there's still time. I can come out.
Move.
(Adam Blake, England Representative)
I'm not interested in men's bodies.
Even Tokimitsu lost
the muscle battle.
Crap. Speed, prediction, ball control,
height, even muscle battle...
all our skills were defeated.
Everything we learned at Blue Lock so far,
it's all useless.
At our current level,
it's absolutely impossible to surpass them.
This is the skill gap
between us and the best players in the world.
They are my target.
Football is truly incredible.
I want to go and reach that level.
It's not over yet.
Still... not over.
Rin?
(Leonardo Luna, Spain Representative)
I really like you.
You are indeed Sae Itoshi's younger brother.
You're different from the others,
you truly wanted to defeat us.
Then, I will beat you with all my strength.
This shouldn't be.
If you open your legs that easily,
you'll be thought of as careless.
Don't be sad, this match was just
to evaluate your abilities.
Essentially,
you couldn't have won anyway.
Report their abilities to Ego.
See you later,
unpolished talents.
See you on the real field.
(Blue Lock, Third Selection)
(First Round,
Fight Against World-Class Players)
Rin...
Damn it!
(Lost)
(Blue Lock, Special Meeting Room)
Give each of them 100 million
to those world-class players.
Score one point, add one million.
Such a reckless project, how much money
will you spend before you're satisfied?
Right, explain to me
what the goal of doing this is?
Then, sit properly!
If you love a child,
let them see the outside world.
(Blue Lock Project Leader, Jinpachi Ego)
Stimulation should be at this reckless age.
Adults who have long given up,
I don't expect you to have dreams,
so shut up and stay silent.
Rude!
Enough already, Ego.
(Advisor, Hirotoshi Buratsuta)
End the Blue Lock project.
Why so suddenly?
The players' parents keep complaining
because the project hasn't been clearly announced.
Most importantly,
there have been no results at all so far,
it's best to end this joke immediately.
Alright then, I'll show you
the results.
Chairman, this is a big match.
The time for Blue Lock to change Japan has come.
(Third Selection, Five-Person Room)
We have no way to handle the opponents.
Yes, I thought I became stronger
after coming to Blue Lock,
now I finally realized
my own ability.
But, somehow
or because I followed
the matches on TV?
Now I finally truly understand
what number one in the world means.
I understand,
the world's number one striker
is no longer a dream.
Even though it's very far, it's real.
This realization is the meaning
of that match.
But,
that person is different.
Only he fought to defeat the world-class
player until the very end of the competition.
After being shocked
by that incredible power,
my mood changed to wanting to learn
from them during the match,
I should have been happy to be able to play
against the opponents I wanted.
This was the reality that I had worked so hard.
So,
Rin, being able to regret like that
is truly amazing.
For me, the world is still
something I aspire to.
While for you, they are
equal opponents who must be defeated.
I'm sure, only someone like him can
compete to become number one in the world.
Rin, I want to be
in the closest place to you,
to surpass you and become number one in the world.
(Third Selection Second Round Very Important
Language Learning From English)
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday,
Wed...
Wedonesday?
The correct one is Wednesday, Stupid!
Aside from Sunday,
you pronounced all the others wrong.
How did you get into high school?
Rin,
when introducing yourself,
instead of my name is, it's better to use I'm, is that right?
Rin,
I'm gently biting my tongue, th.
Th is pronounced like this, right?
(Yoichi Isagi Decides
To Start Learning By Listening)
Rin, tell me,
you're the only one I can rely on.
Th...
is it right or not?
I'm not your private tutor.
I can Friday.
Who can endure days like these?
Actually, how much longer do we have to
go through days like this?
No, to be able to be active on the world stage,
one day it will definitely be useful!
Damn it!
I am sorry, Mustache Prime Minister.
Shave.
- Th... it hurts, I bit my tongue.
- Start again.
The entire second selection just finished.
All the players who advanced
to the third selection have gathered.
It's over?
Are we finally continuing?
- I happened to be bored studying.
- Please wear your uniforms
and gather in the hall immediately.
Alright, the next stage is about to begin.
There are seven teams that passed the second selection,
the total number of players is 35.
Please enter the hall in order.
There are only seven teams,
too many have been eliminated.
Yes.
Initially there were 300 people,
265 people were eliminated.
Did they manage to pass?
Are you missing Team Z?
No, I was just thinking
if they got stronger?
And, to what stage did they evolve?
Just that.
Not just them,
there are other great people, aren't there?
First, the first team that passed
the selection please enter the hall.
(First Team To Pass The Selection
Rin, Aryu, Tokimitsu, Bachira, Isagi)
(Third Selection, Hall)
I feel a little nervous.
Which players passed?
Anyway, the weak ones definitely couldn't pass.
Yes, only those who passed through matches
could make it here.
Next, the second team that passed
the selection please enter the hall.
No matter what way,
I have to reach this place,
only then can I become number one in the world.
Whatever the result, just accept it.
This place is Blue Lock.
(Second Team To Pass
Nagi, Barou, Chigiri, Tsurugi, Kiyora)
Hey!
Trash, I'm here.
Haven't seen you in a million years.
Hey!
Zantetsu is here too.
You guys came too.
You guys...
I'm the 4th person.
He's the 5th person.
Please guide me.
Huh?
Isagi, what's with that relieved expression?
Don't tell me,
you thought we couldn't pass?
No, I didn't...
Don't look at us
with condescending eyes.
Who do you think you are?
It seems, we've been completely
regarded as supporting characters.
I'm not like that.
I'm just really happy.
To be able to meet you guys again,
I'm sincerely happy.
Of course we'll meet again.
I already lost to you,
how could I give up so easily?
I haven't killed you yet
and I haven't beaten the top three.
Just consider it a bad bond
in our fate.
Yeah, if there's a chance,
let's play against each other again.
They really are amazing!
Next is the subsequent team that passed,
please come in.
All of them are people I don't know.
Anyway,
we weren't the only ones playing matches.
Please guide me.
Hello.
In this situation, there's no need to greet, right?
Next is the fourth team that passed,
please come in.
Looks really amazing.
In total, seven teams passed.
So, there are three more teams.
Next is the fifth team that passed,
please come in.
Niko.
I knew you would pass.
We can clash on the soccer field again.
I already told you,
the one who will defeat you is me.
Seems like there's one person missing.
Hajime Nishioka from the fifth team that passed
was injured in the third selection when playing
against the world-class players.
Currently receiving treatment.
That's Nishioka from Aomori High School.
Seems like everyone came here after playing
against the world-class players.
There are two more teams.
They will come, won't they?
Next is the sixth team that passed,
please come in.
I said don't push.
I want to look cool
standing in the middle.
I told you, all of you move aside.
You guys, stop it.
It hurts.
Raichi, Gagamaru!
Stupid, I warned you!
What a terrible entrance.
Hmph!
They still haven't changed.
There are many people
I haven't seen for a long time.
Gagamaru, you...
I said, stand up!
Is big brother Wanima talking?
We can clash again.
One more team left.
Reo and Kunigami still haven't come.
No, they will definitely come.
They are not people who
will stop here.
Finally, the seventh team that passed,
please come in.
Namusan.
Chestnut Head!
Reo.
There is one more person.
The last person is...
Everyone has arrived.
Kunigami...
Where is Kunigami?
These are the players who
managed to pass to the third selection.
Reo, why aren't you with Kunigami?
Why?
We lost,
and I was chosen.
He is not someone who can
become the best striker in the world.
That simple.
Liar!
He... Kunigami's soccer journey,
can't end like this!
It's over.
I was the one who stylishly
kicked him into hell.
His physique was indeed not bad.
His nature was honest, kind-hearted, and naive.
It's just...
no matter how good a nature is,
it's useless on this field.
Someone who relies on momentary explosions,
is nothing more than trash.
That innocent and naive hero,
is nothing more than a slime that cannot
develop in my life.
Watch your mouth!
What do you know about Kunigami?
I told you,
that story between you guys...
is completely useless!
Chigiri?
What's with him? So annoying.
Right. If you want to fight, I'll take you on.
To me, you're the slime,
Burnt Cockroach Mustache.
This is not a burnt color,
it's a healthy wheat color.
Enough, don't fight,
unpolished talents.
You have no time to worry
about those who are eliminated.
Your soccer journey
will soon be fated like Blue Lock,
becoming worthless trash
and disappearing without a trace.
Anyway, everyone,
facing the world-class players
made you feel like a failure, right?
I'll tell you the meaning of it another time.
How to say it?
Because of various reasons,
I have to change the plan.
The higher-ups of Japanese football,
seem to want to destroy Blue Lock.
So, I challenged them.
Therefore, the third selection
in the next three weeks
will determine the life and death of Blue Lock.
A special match:
Japan U20 National Team vs. the Blue Lock Eleven.
As long as we win this match,
Blue Lock will be able to seize
the position of the Japan U20 National Team.
Seize?
Does that mean we will become
the Japan National Team?
We are just a bunch of high school kids.
Besides, all of us are strikers.
So, they accepted this challenge
while looking down on us.
Their goal is
to destroy the Blue Lock plan
and reap profits by taking advantage
of this nationally sensational match.
As a result, if we lose,
besides becoming a laughingstock,
we will be recorded in Japanese soccer history
as a tragic example of failed development.
How do you feel
after hearing this?
Are you upset for being underestimated,
or do you want to show your abilities
and make them stunned?
After considering the current situation
and evaluating calmly,
you, as you are now,
can revolutionize Japanese football.
Even so,
to guarantee their victory,
they have already made various preparations.
Besides deploying active players,
they are including one more person.
Sae Itoshi is joining the Japan team for the first time.
Alright, the time to put everything
on the line has come.
You can already be egoists,
also combining ability and harmony.
After facing the world's best players,
for the 35 of you here,
the throne of the Japan U20 National Team
is no longer just a dream,
but a reality you can grasp
just by reaching out your hand.
Go forward, unpolished talents.
The ones who will change the world, are us,
Blue Lock.
(Episode 24: The Time Has Come)
Isagi, no one is guarding me here!
One for all, all for one.
I used to think, soccer is a sport
where 11 people fight together.
But,
I no longer think so now.
In soccer,
the one who scores is the greatest.
Soccer exists for the striker.
And a striker,
feels happy because they score for themselves.
More than that,
they live for this moment.
I will not fight for you.
Moreover, I will not fight to carry anyone's dream!
I am myself!
This is my own dream,
my own fight.
I am very happy to be able to
play against you.
Therefore, I will keep moving forward
by stepping over your corpses.
Until recently, I was a player no one knew.
Now, if I win, I will become a player for the Japan U20 National Team.
In this match, I will change my life by relying on myself.
We gathered here to win.
Blue Lock cannot end like this.
I will use my goals to change this world.
The one who will become the best striker in the world is...
me!